

Foteinopoulos E

Entry-Level Full Stack Developer

1 9 Ju

9 July 1991

Athens

+30 6976849724

stratosfoteinopoulos .github.io/StratosFotWebsite/

stratosfoteinopoulos@gmail.com

About me —

Junior Developer with multiple skills including multitasking, organization, and collaboration. During my studies and prior job experience, I developed the necessary skills in order to work efficiently, both independently as well as part of a team.

My goals are to learn a variety of skills within the field of programming and work toward deciding what area of specialization I want to take. The first step will be to build a solid foundation and learn the basics in an entry-level role and then become an expert in one specific field.

Skills ———

ASP.NET MVC

SQL

HTML-CSS-Bootstrap

Testing

Front End Frameworks(React-Angular)

(*)[The skill scale is from 0 (Fundamental Awareness) to 6 (Expert).]

Education

2021 PeopleCert Education: CODING BOOTCAMP

A full stack object-oriented programming 500-hour course Courses included:

- ASP.NET MVC C#
- · Relational Databases
- jQuery (JS)
- HTML/CSS/Bootstrap

5-6/2018 SPHY: Greek Military School Of Programming

(https://sphy.army.gr) - Advanced Certification Courses included:

- Installation and configuration of Windows Server
- · Administration of Windows Server
- · Advance Configuration of Windows Server Utilities

1–6/2015 SPHY : Greek Military School Of Programming

(https://sphy.army.gr) - Basic Certification Cources included:

- Networking (Communication Protocols, Configuration)
- Programming Languages (Java, Php, Html)
- Databases (SQL)
- · Security (VPN Firewall)

2009-2011 S.M.Y.N: Hellenic Military School of Cadet Petty Officers Engineer:Rolls-Royce Marine Olympus - Tyne Engines

Work Experience

2021 Accounting Assistant

Responsible for the digitization of office's accounting books and development

of a computerised system.

2020-2021 Ravenna - Manager's Assistant

Naverlina - Manager 3 A3313tant

Responsible for bookkeeping of the warehouse's product operations and $% \left(1\right) =\left(1\right) \left(1$

stacking.

2016-2017 Hellenic Navy -Chief petty officer

IT Manager Assistant with the responsibility of maintaining computer infras-

tructures and assisting users with computers and software issues.

2011-2020 Hellenic Navy-Chief petty officer

ty officer Gas Turbine Engineer

IT Department

Working as an active member of Hellenic Military Navy with the specialty of Engineer. Daily routine included the maintenance and repair of ships engines

and auxiliary systems.

Projects Undertaken

2018 Hellenic Navy Stationed Service

Setup Internal Network of stationed military service at the time

2015 Hellenic Navy Stationed Service

Digitization of ship engines' manuals and Setting up the Internal Network of

stationed military service at the time

Interships

2015 Six months Programming and Networking training in Athens.

[Languages]

Native Greek, Proficient English, Basic French

Interests Software Development , Asp.net Programming using the Agile environment, Creating HTML websites